rangeme.com 2018-08-28

# RangeMe Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy explains how information about you is collected, used and disclosed by RangeMe USA LLC. (“RangeMe”). This Privacy Policy applies to information we collect when you use our website and purchase any of our products or services (collectively, the “Services”) or when you otherwise interact with us.

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make changes, we will notify you by revising the date at the top of the policy and, in some cases, we may provide you with additional notice (such as adding a statement to our homepage or sending you an email notification). We encourage you to review the Privacy Policy whenever you access the Services to stay informed about our information practices and the ways you can help protect your privacy.

#### Collection Of Information

 **Information You Provide to Us**

We collect information you provide directly to us. For example, we collect information when you communicate with us. The types of information we may collect include your name, email address, postal address, phone number, and any other information you choose to provide.

Information We Collect Automatically When You Use the Services

When you access or use our Services, we automatically collect information about you, including:

  * Log Information: We log information about your use of the Services, including the type of browser you use, access times, pages viewed, your IP address and the page you visited before navigating to our Services.
  * Device Information: We collect information about the computer or mobile device you use to access our Services, including the hardware model, operating system and version, unique device identifiers and mobile network information.
  * Information Collected by Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies: We use various technologies to collect information, and this may include sending cookies to your computer or mobile device. Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive or in device memory that help us to improve our Services and your experience, see which areas and features of our Services are popular and count visits. We may also collect information using web beacons (also known as “tracking pixels”). Web beacons are electronic images that may be used in our Services or emails and help deliver cookies, count visits and understand usage and determine whether an email has been opened and acted upon. For more information about cookies, and how to disable them, please see “Your Choices” below.
  * Information We Collect From Other Sources

We may also obtain information from other sources and combine that with information we collect through our Services. For example, we may collect information about you from third parties, including but not limited to identity verification services and credit bureaus.

#### Use Of Information

We may use information about you for various purposes, including to:

  * Provide, maintain and improve our Services;
  * Provide and deliver the products and services you request, process transactions and send you related information, including confirmations and invoices,
  * Communicate with you about products and services;
  * Monitor and analyze trends, usage and activities in connection with our Services; and
  * Carry out any other purpose for which the information was collected.

RangeMe is based in the United States and the information we collect is governed by U.S. law. By accessing or using the Services or otherwise providing information to us, you consent to the processing and transfer of information in and to the U.S. and other countries.

#### Sharing Of Information

We may share information about you as follows or as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy:

  * With vendors, consultants and other service providers who need access to such information to carry out work on our behalf;
  * In response to a request for information if we believe disclosure is in accordance with any applicable law, regulation or legal process, or as otherwise required by any applicable law, rule or regulation;
  * If we believe your actions are inconsistent with the spirit or language of our user agreements or policies, or to protect the rights, property and safety of RangeMe or others;
  * In connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company; and
  * With your consent or at your direction, including if we notify you through our Services that the information you provide will be shared in a particular manner and you provide such information.
  * We may also share aggregated or de-identified information, which cannot reasonably be used to identify you.

#### Social Sharing Features

The Services may offer social sharing features and other integrated tools (such as the Facebook “Like” button), which let you share actions you take on our Services with other media, and vice versa. The use of such features enables the sharing of information with your friends or the public, depending on the settings you establish with the entity that provides the social sharing feature. For more information about the purpose and scope of data collection and processing in connection with social sharing features, please visit the privacy policies of the entities that provide these features.

#### Advertising And Analytics Services Provided By Others

We may allow others to serve advertisements on our behalf across the Internet and to provide analytics services. These entities may use cookies, web beacons and other technologies to collect information about your use of the Services and other websites, including your IP address, web browser, pages viewed, time spent on pages, links clicked and conversion information. This information may be used by Company and others to, among other things, analyze and track data, determine the popularity of certain content, deliver advertising and content targeted to your interests on our Services and other websites and better understand your online activity. For more information about Internet-based ads, or to opt out of having your web browsing information used for behavioral advertising purposes, please visit[ www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp ](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)and[ www.aboutads.info/choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices)

#### Security

RangeMe takes reasonable measures to help protect information about you from loss, theft, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction.

#### Your Choices

 **Account Information**

You may update, correct or delete information about you at any time by logging into your online account, emailing us at team@rangeme.com. If you wish to delete or deactivate your account, please email us at team@rangemem.com, but note that we may retain certain information as required by law or for legitimate business purposes. We may also retain cached or archived copies of information about you for a certain period of time.

 **Cookies**

Most web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually choose to set your browser to remove or reject browser cookies. Please note that if you choose to remove or reject cookies, this could affect the availability and functionality of our Services.

 **Marketing and Promotional Communications**

You may opt out of receiving promotional emails from RangeMe by following the instructions in those emails or by emailing team@rangeme.com and requesting to be removed from our mailing list. If you opt out, we may still send you non-promotional communications, such as those about your account or our ongoing business relations.

 **Your California Privacy Rights**

California law permits residents of California to request certain details about how their information is shared with third parties for direct marketing purposes. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please contact us at questions@rangeme.com. However, please note that under the law, Services such as ours that permit California residents to opt in to, or opt out of, this type of sharing are not required to provide such information upon receiving a request, but rather may respond by notifying the user of his or her right to prevent the disclosure. To opt out of having information about you shared with third parties for direct marketing purposes, please contact[ support@rangeme.com](mailto:support@rangeme.com).

#### Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at:[ questions@rangeme.com](mailto:questions@rangeme.com).
